Yakantan Idol regards!
Well, it's an early ending.
Do you have any news from Ayano-san?
Yes, I do.
Our mini album "Coffee" will be released on May 16.
Yay!
Which album?
This one is a bit more mature and relaxed, whereas we at AmeFlash have always expressed a cool and mature look,
This time it's a bit more relaxed and mature,
We are trying to express a calm and mature atmosphere, or maybe a little bit of sexiness,
We want to express a bit of maturity,
This mini-album is about expressing our mature and grown-up side.
What's that? You're putting it over coffee?
Is it something that is played in cafes?
Or music that is comfortable to listen to?
I think AmeFlash has a lot of gutsy music,
I think AmeFlash has a lot of gutsy music, but some of the songs are a bit ballad-like,
I don't want to spoil anything,
I shouldn't say this.
I'm a person who can't give away spoilers,
I don't like spoilers.
I'm the type of person who tells things right away.
I'm the one who tells too.
You're a spoiler?
Too much.
Too much?
Yes, too much.
I do it in the image of my love,
I'm the kind of person who does a lot of it,
That's right.
I don't know how to get it just right.
We don't know.
So, it's the kind of song you'd want to listen to on the beach,
Or mature songs that you can listen to when you want to get excited,
We have a variety of songs in the album,
Please listen to it.
It will be released on May 16.
But, and also...,
We will also have a lot of releases until the end of May,
We are going to have a lot of releases until the end of May, so we will be in various places such as Toyosu and Odaiba,
Tower Records in Shibuya, and so on,
We will also have a lot of releases until the end of May, so please come to Toyosu, Odaiba, Tower Records in Shibuya, and so on,
Please come and visit us if you like. Please come and visit us.
Please come and visit us.
And on Sunday, July 9, Biosign 2023 will be held in Shinjuku.
Yay!
What kind of event is this?
This event started last year,
We want to make it a regular summer event at Amagrash,
It is a two-part event,
Last year, we collaborated with Japanese drums,
Japanese drums?
That's right. With big taiko drums.
So you had taiko in the AmeFlash Music Hall.
Yes. It was a great match,
It was cool all of a sudden,
I put it on YouTube the other day,
I put it on YouTube the other day, so you can watch it if you want,
I hope you all enjoy what we have in store for you this year,
Please come and enjoy the show.
Yes, July 9.
Now, Yagin-kun is giving away a cup of tea to cheer you up at the end of the show,
This time, it's coffee, which will be released on May 16.
Coffee?
Coffee.
I'll have you drink it.
Do you drink coffee because of your character?
I don't drink much coffee.
That's right.
That's right. You're an adult.
No, no, no. You're not an adult.
I turned 20.
You've turned 20.
Then, I'll have it.
Yes, it's good. It's delicious.
Ha-ha-ha!
That's why I was the alarm clock.
Really? Did I sound like I'm impressed just now?
You're learning how to work up an appetite with the director, aren't you?
Yes, that's right. You know how they say you can't have too much information?
Too much information is bad?
If there are more than three, such as "it is sweet, salty, and pleasant to the tongue," the information gets confusing, so I am told to keep it simple.
Simple? That's very current.
You say it simply.
I got it simply.
Yes, I got it. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I am sorry for this last one, Aira-san. This is something we always receive from you.
If you could close this program in a cute way for the camera.
It will be the end of the program.
Yes.
The theme of this program is to be cute.
That's right. Then, let's go.
Please do.
If you are interested in Aira today, definitely come see her.
That's all for now, this is Shinai Aira Ameura.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ya, easy idol!
Yes!
This program is
Toshikazu
Naosan
Chie
Takesan
and Hanarin-san.
Thank you very much!